Guide to the Gregory Breit Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1932-1973; Series I; 14.5 linear feet (29 boxes)
  - Consultants Bureau, Inc., 1958, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 171, Reel 3U)
  - Coral Gables Conference, 1964, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 172, Reel 3U)
  - Cormack, A. M., 1966 (Box 5, Folder 173, Reel 3U)
  - Cornell University, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 174, Reel 3U)
    Laboratory of Nuclear Studies
  - Corson, Edward M., 1953-1954, 1957, undated (Box 5, Folder 175, Reel 3U)
  - Cottingham, W. W., 1962 (Box 5, Folder 176, Reel 3U)
  - Courant, Hans, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 177, Reel 3U)
  - Courant, R., 1953 (Box 5, Folder 178, Reel 3U)
  - Cox, Richard T., 1934, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 179, Reel 3U)
  - Cranberg, Lawrence, 1964, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 180, Reel 3U)
  - Crannell, Hall, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 181, Reel 3U)
  - Crawford, Bryce D., 1968 (Box 5, Folder 182, Reel 3U)
  - Cretella, Albert W., 1958 (Box 5, Folder 183, Reel 3U)
  - Creutz, Edward, 1942, 1954, 1957-1958, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 184, Reel 3U)
  - Crew, W. H., 1957 (Box 5, Folder 185, Reel 3U)
  - Cromer, Alan H., 1967 (Box 5, Folder 186, Reel 3U)
  - Cronin, J. W., 1970 (Box 5, Folder 187, Reel 3U)
  - Crowe, K. M., 1971 (Box 5, Folder 188, Reel 3U)
  - Culver Military Academy, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 189, Reel 3U)
  - Daitch, P. B., 1952 (Box 6, Folder 190, Reel 3U)
  - Dalitz, Richard H., 1959, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 191, Reel 3U)
  - Dall'Asta, Eberhard R., 1971 (Box 6, Folder 192, Reel 3U)
  - Danielli, James F., 1973 (Box 6, Folder 193, Reel 3U)
  - Danos, Michael, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 194, Reel 3U)
  - Darling, Bryan T., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 195, Reel 3U)
  - Darrow, Karl K., 1951-1955, 1957, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 196, Reel 3U)
  - Davis, J. C., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 197, Reel 3U)
  - Davis, P. J., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 198, Reel 3U)
  - Dawson, John W., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 199, Reel 3U)
  - Dawson, Peter C., 1970 (Box 6, Folder 200, Reel 3U)
  - Dawson, William L., 1958 (Box 6, Folder 201, Reel 3U)
  - de Boer, Jorrit, 1963, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 202, Reel 3U)
  - Delhi University, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 203, Reel 3U)
  - Demeur, M., 1957, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 204, Reel 3U)
  - Dennison, David M., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 205, Reel 3U)
  - Deutsche Physikalische Gesellschaft (German Physical Society), 1953, 1955-1964, 1966-1967, 1969, undated (Box 6, Folder 206, Reel 3U)
  - DeVane, William, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 207, Reel 4U)
  - Devons, Samuel, 1955-1958, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 208, Reel 4U)
  - de Wit, Michiel, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 209, Reel 4U)
  - De Witt, Bryce S., 1956 (Box 6, Folder 210, Reel 4U)
  - Dirac, P. A. M., 1962, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 211, Reel 4U)
  - Douglas, Paul H., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 212, Reel 4U)
  - Drell, Sidney D., 1960, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 213, Reel 4U)
  - Droessler, Earl G., 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 214, Reel 4U)
  - Dryden, Hugh Latimer, 1962, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 215, Reel 4U)
  - DuBridge, Lee A., 1961, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 216, Reel 4U)
  - DuMond, Jesse W. M., 1960-1961, 1964-1965, 1968, 1970, undated (Box 6, Folder 217, Reel 4U)
  - Dunipace, D. W., 1956 (Box 6, Folder 218, Reel 4U)
  - Dunn, L. C., 1933 (Box 6, Folder 219, Reel 4U)
  - Du Pont Company, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 220, Reel 4U)
  - Durand, Loyal III, 1956, 1960, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 221, Reel 4U)
  - Dyson, Freeman, 1962, 1966, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 222, Reel 4U)
  - E. E. Wyatt and Associates, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 223, Reel 4U)
  - Eastern Theoretical Physics Conferences, 1962-1965 (Box 6, Folder 224, Reel 4U)
  - Eastern Theoretical Physics Conferences, 1966-1969, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 225, Reel 4U)
  - Ebel, Marvin E., 1957, 1960, 1968, undated (Box 6, Folder 226, Reel 4U)
  - Eden, Richard J., 1955, 1957, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 227, Reel 4U)
  - Editrice Compositori s.r.l., 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 228, Reel 4U)
  - Ellett, Alexander, 1934, 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 229, Reel 4U)
  - Endt, P. M., 1956-1957 (Box 6, Folder 230, Reel 4U)
  - Epler, Robert E., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 231, Reel 4U)
  - Erdèlyi, A., 1954 (Box 6, Folder 232, Reel 4U)
  - Erickson, K. W., 1953, undated (Box 6, Folder 233, Reel 4U)
  - European Conference on Nuclear Physics (Conférence Européenne de Physique Nucléaire), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 234, Reel 4U)
  - Executive Office of the President, 1968, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 235, Reel 4U)
    Office of Science and Technology
  - Fairbank, Henry A., 1968, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 236, Reel 4U)
  - Fairfax Hotel, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 237, Reel 4U)
  - Fairfield University, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 238, Reel 4U)
  - Fajans, K., 1932 (Box 6, Folder 239, Reel 4U)
  - Far Eastern Trading Co., Ltd., 1950 (Box 6, Folder 240, Reel 4U)
  - Farmer, W. W., 1962 (Box 6, Folder 241, Reel 4U)
  - Feenberg, Eugene, 1937, 1940, 1946, 1949, 1953, 1957-1961, 1973, undated (Box 6, Folder 242, Reel 4U)
  - Feinberg, G., 1958 (Box 6, Folder 243, Reel 4U)
  - Feldman, David, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 244, Reel 4U)
  - Felton, J. S., 1966 (Box 6, Folder 245, Reel 4U)
  - Fermi, Laura, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 246, Reel 4U)
  - Feshbach, Herman, 1954-1957, 1959, 1962, 1966-1970 (Box 6, Folder 247, Reel 4U)
  - Feynman, R. F., 1954, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 248, Reel 4U)
  - Firk, F. W. K., 1967, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 249, Reel 4U)
  - First National Bank and Trust Company, 1946, 1948, 1951-1953, 1955-1959 (Box 7, Folder 250, Reel 4U)
  - Fischer, C. Rutherford, 1964, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 251, Reel 4U)
  - Fischer, Vera K., 1958 (Box 7, Folder 252, Reel 4U)
  - Fisk, James B., 1960 (Box 7, Folder 253, Reel 4U)
  - Flerov, G. N., 1964-1967, undated (Box 7, Folder 254, Reel 4U)
  - Florida State University, 1957, 1959, 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 255, Reel 4U)
  - Flügge, S., 1955-1960 (Box 7, Folder 256, Reel 4U)
  - Foldy, Leslie L., 1956-1957, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 257, Reel 4U)
  - Foley, Henry M., 1955, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 258, Reel 4U)
  - Foundations of Quantum Mechanics (conference), 1947 (Box 7, Folder 259, Reel 4U)
  - Four Continent Book Corporation, 1958, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 260, Reel 4U)
  - Fowler, J. L., 1954, 1957, 1959, 1963, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 261, Reel 4U)
  - Fowler, William A., 1967, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 262, Reel 4U)
  - Francis, Norman C., 1959. 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 263, Reel 4U)
  - Franklin Institute, 1963-1969, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 264, Reel 4U)
  - Fred, E. B., 1954, undated (Box 7, Folder 265, Reel 4U)
  - Freeman, Burton E., 1952, 1956, 1958, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 266, Reel 4U)
  - Frenkel, Victor J., 1967, 1969, 1971, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 267, Reel 4U)
  - Friedman, K. A., 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 268, Reel 4U)
  - Friedrichs, K. O., 1963 (Box 7, Folder 269, Reel 4U)
  - Fröman, Nanny, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 270, Reel 4U)
  - Fuda, M. G., undated (Box 7, Folder 271, Reel 4U)
  - Fulbright, J. W., 1968 (Box 7, Folder 272, Reel 4U)
  - Fulton, T., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 273, Reel 4U)
  - Furniss, Edgar S., 1951, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 274, Reel 4U)
  - Gammel, John L., 1952, 1956-1957, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 275, Reel 4U)
  - Gamow, George, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 276, Reel 4U)
  - Gartenhaus, Solomon, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 277, Reel 4U)
  - Gell-Mann, Murray, 1958, 1961, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 278, Reel 4U)
  - General Dynamics Electric Boat Division, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 279, Reel 4U)
  - General Electric Company, 1941, 1947, 1951, 1956-1957, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 280, Reel 4U)
  - General Electric Company, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 281, Reel 4U)
  - Georgia Institute of Technology, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 282, Reel 4U)
  - Gerjuoy, Edward, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 283, Reel 4U)
  - Gibbs, R. C., 1933 (Box 7, Folder 284, Reel 4U)
  - Gibson, Jacqueline, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 285, Reel 4U)
  - Gibson, Ralph E., 1962, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 286, Reel 4U)
  - Gien, Tran T., 1964 (Box 7, Folder 287, Reel 4U)
  - Gilbertson, Edna, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 288, Reel 4U)
  - Gillmor, C. Stewart, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 289, Reel 4U)
  - Glass, Alexander J., 1960, 1963-1964, 1967, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 290, Reel 4U)
  - Gluckstern, Robert L., 1950, 1954, 1956, 1958, 1962-1965, 1967-1968, undated (Box 7, Folder 291, Reel 4U)
  - Gmelin Institute, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 292, Reel 4U)
  - Goldansky, V. I., 1960 (Box 7, Folder 293, Reel 4U)
  - Goldberger, Marvin L., 1963-1964, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 294, Reel 4U)
  - Goldfarb, L. J. B., 1956-1957, 1964, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 295, Reel 4U)
  - Goldhaber, Gertrude Scharf, 1953, 1958, 1963-1964, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 296, Reel 4U)
  - Goldhaber, Maurice, 1958, 1960, 1963, 1968, 1970, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 297, Reel 4U)
  - Goloskie, Raymond, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 298, Reel 4U)
  - Good, Roland H., 1964 (Box 7, Folder 299, Reel 4U)
  - Goodell, Charles, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 300, Reel 4U)
  - Gorbunov, A. N., 1964, undated (Box 8, Folder 301, Reel 5U)
  - Gordon and Breach Science Publishers, Inc., 1963-1964 (Box 8, Folder 302, Reel 5U)
  - Gordon Research Conferences, 1965-1968 (Box 8, Folder 303, Reel 5U)
  - Goudsmit, Samuel A., 1933, 1951, 1958, 1960, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 304, Reel 5U)
  - Gove, H. E., 1969 (Box 8, Folder 305, Reel 5U)
  - Governor Clinton Hotel, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 306, Reel 5U)
  - Graduate Club Association, 1947, 1951, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 307, Reel 5U)
  - Graduate Record Office, 1946 (Box 8, Folder 308, Reel 5U)
  - Graduate Research Center, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 309, Reel 5U)
  - Graham Travel Company, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 310, Reel 5U)
  - Gray, George W., 1933 (Box 8, Folder 311, Reel 5U)
  - Grebe, John J., 1964 (Box 8, Folder 312, Reel 5U)
  - Green, Alex E. S., 1959-1960, 1967-1971, undated (Box 8, Folder 313-314, Reel 5U)
  - Green, Louis C., 1956 (Box 8, Folder 315, Reel 5U)
  - Griggs, Henry L., 1956-1958, 1960, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 316, Reel 5U)
  - Griswold, A. Whitney, 1952, 1954, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 317, Reel 5U)
  - Grodzins, Lee, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 318, Reel 5U)
  - Grönblom, B. O., 1939, undated (Box 8, Folder 319, Reel 5U)
  - Gürsey, Feza, 1958, 1963, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 320, Reel 5U)
  - Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1935, 1939, 1951-1952, 1958-1959, 1961, 1968, undated (Box 8, Folder 321, Reel 5U)
  - Gull Lake Symposium on the Two-Body Force in Nuclei, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 322, Reel 5U)
  - Gunn, Ross, 1960, undated (Box 8, Folder 323, Reel 5U)
  - Gupta, Saraj N., 1957-1970, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 324-328, Reel 5U)
  - Hadjmichael, Vagos, 1966, 1969, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 329, Reel 5U)
  - Haeberli, W., 1959 (Box 8, Folder 330, Reel 5U)
  - Hafstad, L. R., 1968 (Box 8, Folder 331, Reel 5U)
  - Hagen, C. R., 1968 (Box 8, Folder 332, Reel 5U)
  - Hahn, Yukap, 1961-1962, 1964-1965, 1967-1971 (Box 8, Folder 333, Reel 5U)
  - Halbert, Edith C., 1960 (Box 8, Folder 334, Reel 5U)
  - Halbert, M. L., undated (Box 8, Folder 335, Reel 5U)
  - Halpern, Francis R., 1969 (Box 8, Folder 336, Reel 5U)
  - Halpern, Julius, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 337, Reel 5U)
  - Ham, Frank S., 1955 (Box 8, Folder 338, Reel 5U)
  - Hamada, T., 1961 (Box 8, Folder 339, Reel 5U)
  - Hannum, R. W., 1967 (Box 8, Folder 340, Reel 5U)
  - Hanson, A. O., 1962, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 341, Reel 5U)
  - Haracz, Richard, 1966, 1968-1969, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 342, Reel 5U)
  - Harris, Oren, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 343, Reel 5U)
  - Harrison, Don E., 1968 (Box 9, Folder 344, Reel 5U)
  - Harrison, Ralph J., 1970 (Box 9, Folder 345, Reel 5U)
  - Hartree, Douglas R., 1957 (Box 9, Folder 346, Reel 5U)
  - Harvard University, 1953, 1955-1958, 1960, 1963, 1965-1966 (Box 9, Folder 347, Reel 5U)
  - Hartmann, George C., 1967 (Box 9, Folder 348, Reel 5U)
  - Hatcher, Robert D., 1956 (Box 9, Folder 349, Reel 5U)
  - Harvey, J. A., 1967 (Box 9, Folder 350, Reel 5U)
  - Havel, James, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 351, Reel 5U)
  - Havens, William W., Jr., 1954, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 352, Reel 5U)
  - Haworth, Leland J., 1937-1938, 1953, 1968, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 353, Reel 5U)
  - Hayward, Evans, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 354, Reel 5U)
  - Haywood, Colonel Oliver, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 355, Reel 5U)
  - Heberle, Juergen, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 356, Reel 5U)
  - Heisenberg, J., 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 357, Reel 5U)
  - Heisenberg, Werner, 1950-1951, 1954, 1958, 1963, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 358, Reel 5U)
  - Heitler, W., 1940 (Box 9, Folder 359, Reel 5U)
  - Heller, William R., 1952, 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 360, Reel 5U)
  - Hendel, Charles W., 1959 (Box 9, Folder 361, Reel 5U)
  - Henkel, Richard L., 1957-1958 (Box 9, Folder 362, Reel 5U)
  - Henley, Ernest M., 1972 (Box 9, Folder 363, Reel 5U)
  - Herb, Raymond G., 1944-1945, 1948, 1954-1958, 1963, 1968, 1970-1971, undated (Box 9, Folder 364, Reel 5U)
  - Herling, Gary H., 1956-1957, 1960-1962, 1964, 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 365, Reel 5U)
  - Herschman, Arthur, 1956-1957, undated (Box 9, Folder 366, Reel 5U)
  - Herzberg, G., 1955, 1958, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 367, Reel 5U)
  - Herzfeld, K. F., 1934, undated (Box 9, Folder 368, Reel 5U)
  - Hestenes, Arnold D., 1953 (Box 9, Folder 369, Reel 5U)
  - Heydenburg, Norman P., 1955-1956, 1959-1960, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 370, Reel 5U)
  - High Voltage Engineering Corporation, 1948, 1951-1952, 1956, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 371, Reel 5U)
  - Hill, David L., 1955-1956 (Box 9, Folder 372, Reel 5U)
  - Hirschfelder, Joseph O., 1948, 1956, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 373, Reel 6U)
  - Hofstadter, Robert, 1955-1958, 1960-1964, 1969, 1973, undated (Box 9, Folder 374, Reel 6U)
  - Holt, J. R., 1956 (Box 9, Folder 375, Reel 6U)
  - Holt, Rinehart, and Winston, Inc., 1965 (Box 9, Folder 376, Reel 6U)
  - Hopkins, John C., 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 377, Reel 6U)
  - Hornig, Donald F., 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 378, Reel 6U)
  - Hotel New Yorker, 1951, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 379, Reel 6U)
  - Hotel Somerset, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 380, Reel 6U)
  - Hotel Washington, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 381, Reel 6U)
  - Hotel Windsor Park, 1961, 1963, 1966, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 382, Reel 6U)
  - Howard, Frederick T., 1958 (Box 10, Folder 383, Reel 6U)
  - Huby, R., 1958 (Box 10, Folder 384, Reel 6U)
  - Hudson, Colin M., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 385, Reel 6U)
  - Huebner, Walter F., 1958-1959, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 386, Reel 6U)
  - Hughes, Vernon Willard, 1952-1954, 1961, 1963-1969, 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 387, Reel 6U)
  - Hulburt, Edward O., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 388, Reel 6U)
  - Hull, Gordon Ferrie, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 389, Reel 6U)
  - Hull, McAllister H., Jr., 1950-1958, 1963-1969, 1971, undated (Box 10, Folder 390-393, Reel 6U)
  - Humphrey, Charles H., 1953, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 394, Reel 6U)
  - Hunter College, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 395, Reel 6U)
  - Hurst, R. P., 1971 (Box 10, Folder 396, Reel 6U)
  - Hussein, H. M., 1971 (Box 10, Folder 397, Reel 6U)
  - Hylleraas, E. A., 1956 (Box 10, Folder 398, Reel 6U)
  - I. R. Maxwell and Company, Inc., 1953, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 399, Reel 6U)
  - Igo, George J., 1954-1956, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 400, Reel 6U)
  - Indiana University, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 401, Reel 6U)
  - Ingersoll, Leonard R., 1938, 1940-1947, undated (Box 10, Folder 402-403, Reel 6U)
  - Inglis, David R., 1949, 1955, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 404, Reel 6U)
  - Institut für Theoretische Physik der Universität Basel, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 405, Reel 6U)
  - Institut für Theoretische Physik der Universität Graz, 1965-1966 (Box 10, Folder 406, Reel 6U)
  - Institute for Advanced Study, 1934, 1939, 1954-1955, 1972-1973, undated (Box 10, Folder 407, Reel 6U)
  - Institute for Defense Analyses, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 408, Reel 6U)
  - Institute for Mechanics and Mathematical Physics, 1952 (Box 10, Folder 409, Reel 6U)
  - Institute for Theoretical Physics, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 410, Reel 6U)
  - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers, Inc. (IEEE), 1963, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 411, Reel 6U)
  - Institute of International, Education, 1951 (Box 10, Folder 412, Reel 6U)
  - Institute of Physics and The Physical Society, 1939-1940, 1946-1948, 1951, 1953, 1955-1962, 1964-1966, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 413, Reel 6U)
  - Institute of Physics and The Physical Society, 1970, 1972, undated (Box 10, Folder 414, Reel 6U)
  - Institute of Radio Engineers, 1949-1955 (Box 10, Folder 415, Reel 6U)
  - International Advanced School for Theoretical Physics, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 416, Reel 6U)
  - International Atomic Energy Agency, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 417, Reel 6U)
  - International Business Machines Corporation (IBM), 1951, 1953, 1958-1960 (Box 11, Folder 418, Reel 6U)
  - International Centre for Theoretical Physics, 1969, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 419, Reel 6U)
  - International Conference on Atomic Physics, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 420, Reel 6U)
  - International Conference on Electromagnetic Sizes of Nuclei, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 421, Reel 6U)
  - International Conference on "Few Particle Problems in Nuclear Interaction", 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 422, Reel 6U)
  - International Conference on Heavy Ion Physics, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 423, Reel 6U)
  - International Conference on High Energy Physics, 1964-1966 (Box 11, Folder 424, Reel 6U)
  - International Conference on Low and Intermediate Energy Electromagnetic Interactions, 1966-1967 (Box 11, Folder 425, Reel 6U)
  - International Conference on Nuclear Moments and Nuclear Structure, 1971-1973 (Box 11, Folder 426, Reel 6U)
  - International Conference on Nuclear Physics, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 427, Reel 6U)
  - International Conference on Nuclear Reaction Induced by Heavy Ions, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 428, Reel 6U)
  - International Conference on Nuclear Structure, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 429, Reel 6U)
  - International Conference on Photonuclear Reactions and Applications, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 430, Reel 6U)
  - International Conference on Properties of Nuclear States (Conférence Internationale sur les Propriétés des Etats Nucléaires), 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 431, Reel 6U)
  - International Conference on Statistical Properties of Nuclei, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 432, Reel 6U)
  - International Conference on Symmetries and Quark Models, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 433, Reel 6U)
  - International Conference on the Physics of Electronic and Atomic Collisions, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 434, Reel 6U)
  - International Conference on the Three-Body Problem in Nuclear and Particle Physics, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 435, Reel 6U)
  - International Platform Association, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 436, Reel 6U)
  - International Science Foundation, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 437, Reel 6U)
  - International Symposium on Atomic and Molecular Quantum Mechanics, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 438, Reel 6U)
  - International Symposium on Atomic, Molecular, and Solid-State Theory and Quantum Biology, 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 439, Reel 6U)
  - International Symposium on Contemporary Physics, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 440, Reel 6U)
  - International Symposium on Polarization Phenomena in Nuclear Reactions, 1965, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 441, Reel 7U)
  - International Theoretical Physics Conference on Particles and Fields, 1967-1968 (Box 11, Folder 442, Reel 7U)
  - Interscience Publishers, Inc., 1960 (Box 11, Folder 443, Reel 7U)
  - Iowa State University, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 444, Reel 7U)
    Department of Physics
  - Ishidzu, Takehiko, 1951 (Box 11, Folder 445, Reel 7U)
  - Istituti di Fisica, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 446, Reel 7U)
  - Jackson, J. David, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 447, Reel 7U)
  - Jafar, J. O., 1965 (Box 11, Folder 448, Reel 7U)
  - Jain, Piyare L., 1969 (Box 11, Folder 449, Reel 7U)
  - Jancovici, Bernard G., 1954 (Box 11, Folder 450, Reel 7U)
  - Jarmie, Nelson, 1961, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 451, Reel 7U)
  - Jastrow, Robert, 1948-1956, 1967, undated (Box 11, Folder 452, Reel 7U)
  - Jauch, J. M., 1957 (Box 11, Folder 453, Reel 7U)
  - Javits, Jacob, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 454, Reel 7U)
  - Jefferson City (Georgia) Schools, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 455, Reel 7U)
  - Jensen, J. Hans D., 1963-1964, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 456, Reel 7U)
  - Johann, Robert, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 457, Reel 7U)
  - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 458, Reel 7U)
  - John Wiley & Sons, Inc., 1946-1947, 1950-1952, 1955, 1957-1959, 1961, 1963-1965, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 459-460, Reel 7U)
  - Johns Hopkins University, 1945-1949, 1951, 1958-1959, 1961, 1966, [1968], 1972 (Box 12, Folder 461, Reel 7U)
  - Johnson, Ellis A., 1949-1950 (Box 12, Folder 462, Reel 7U)
  - Johnson, John L., 1955, 1959, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 463, Reel 7U)
  - Johnston, Lawrence H., 1957, 1959-1960 (Box 12, Folder 464, Reel 7U)
  - Johnston, Robert W., 1968 (Box 12, Folder 465, Reel 7U)
  - Joint Institute for Nuclear Research, 1964, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 466, Reel 7U)
  - Jones, D. T. L., 1972 (Box 12, Folder 467, Reel 7U)
  - Jones, Harrison Milas, 1952-1956 (Box 12, Folder 468, Reel 7U)
  - Joshi, G. C., 1969 (Box 12, Folder 469, Reel 7U)
  - Journal of Atmospheric and Terrestrial Physics, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 470, Reel 7U)
  - Journal of Chemical Physics, 1959-1961, 1965, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 471, Reel 7U)
  - Journal of the Franklin Institute, 1964-1965, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 472, Reel 7U)
  - Jungk, Robert, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 473, Reel 7U)
  - Källén, Gunnar, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 474, Reel 7U)
  - Kanne, W. R., 1968 (Box 12, Folder 475, Reel 7U)
  - Kansas State College Department of Physics, 1958-1960 (Box 12, Folder 476, Reel 7U)
  - Kaplan, Joseph, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 477, Reel 7U)
  - Karzmark, Clarence J., 1947 (Box 12, Folder 478, Reel 7U)
  - Katz, L., 1956 (Box 12, Folder 479, Reel 7U)
  - Kaveeshivar, V. G., 1968 (Box 12, Folder 480, Reel 7U)
  - Kazarinov, Yu M., 1964-1966, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 481, Reel 7U)
  - Keller, Charles A., 1947 (Box 12, Folder 482, Reel 7U)
  - Keller, Harold, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 483, Reel 7U)
  - Kellogg, H. Dudley, Jr., 1964, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 484, Reel 7U)
  - Kellogg, J. M. B., 1957 (Box 12, Folder 485, Reel 7U)
  - Kemmer, N., 1939 (Box 12, Folder 486, Reel 7U)
  - Kent, Robert H., 1947-1953, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 487, Reel 7U)
  - Kerman, Arthur, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 488, Reel 7U)
  - Kerst, Donald W., 1937-1942, 1945-1947, 1951, 1957, 1960-1961, 1968, 1971, undated (Box 12, Folder 489, Reel 7U)
  - Khanduri, Nawin C., 1965, 1970-1971, n.d (Box 12, Folder 490, Reel 7U)
    See also: box 9, folder 345
  - Kilpatrick, Robert H., 1968 (Box 12, Folder 491, Reel 7U)
  - Kirkman, Robert W., 1953 (Box 12, Folder 492, Reel 7U)
  - Kirkwood, John G., 1955-1957 (Box 12, Folder 493, Reel 7U)
  - Kistiakowsky, George B., 1972 (Box 12, Folder 494, Reel 7U)
  - Kittel, Charles, 1941-1950, 1952-1958, 1968, undated (Box 12, Folder 495-497, Reel 7U)
  - Klarsfeld, S., 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 498, Reel 7U)
  - Klauder, John R., 1947, 1970-1971, undated (Box 12, Folder 499, Reel 7U)
  - Kleene, Stephen C., 1969 (Box 12, Folder 500, Reel 7U)
  - Kleiman, Joseph, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 501, Reel 7U)
  - Klein, Martin J., 1956 (Box 13, Folder 502, Reel 7U)
  - Knecht, David J., 1957-1958, 1960-1961, 1963, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 503, Reel 7U)
  - Knipp, Julian K., 1954-1956 (Box 13, Folder 504, Reel 7U)
  - Knowles, H. B., 1963-1966, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 505, Reel 7U)
  - Knox, William J., 1951 (Box 13, Folder 506, Reel 7U)
  - Kobayasi, Minoru, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 507, Reel 7U)
  - Kocevar, Peter, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 508, Reel 7U)
  - Koch, H. William, 1956, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 509, Reel 7U)
  - Kolomensky, A. A., 1966 (Box 13, Folder 510, Reel 7U)
  - Kolstad, George A., 1950-1951, 1953-1956, 1959, 1963-1965 (Box 13, Folder 511, Reel 7U)
  - Konopinski, E. J., 1968 (Box 13, Folder 512, Reel 7U)
  - Kopfermann, Hans, 1950-1952, 1958, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 513, Reel 7U)
  - Korff, Serge A., 1939, 1954, undated (Box 13, Folder 514, Reel 7U)
  - Kowalski, K. L., 1963 (Box 13, Folder 515, Reel 7U)
  - Kramers, H. A., 1946 (Box 13, Folder 516, Reel 7U)
  - Kuhn, Thomas S., 1963-1964 (Box 13, Folder 517, Reel 7U)
  - Kursunoglu, Behram, 1954-1956, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 518, Reel 7U)
  - Kursunoglu, Behram, 1965-1969 (Box 13, Folder 519, Reel 7U)
  - Kusch, P., 1947-1948, 1966, 1968-1969 (Box 13, Folder 520, Reel 7U)
  - Kyoto University, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 521, Reel 7U)